<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Dev Gear Reviews</title><link>https://DavidDevGear.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Dev Gear Reviews</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://DavidDevGear.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Budget Audio King</title><link>https://DavidDevGear.github.io/reviews/kz-zsn-pro-x/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://DavidDevGear.github.io/reviews/kz-zsn-pro-x/</guid><description>Overview The KZ ZSN Pro X has built a reputation as one of the best budget IEMs on Amazon. Drawing from thousands of user reviews and audio forums, this earphone consistently stands out for sound quality that far exceeds its price.
Sound Quality Based on aggregated reviews:
Bass: Punchy and energetic, slightly boosted Mids: Clear vocals, good separation Treble: Bright and detailed, can be sharp at high volumes For gaming and casual listening, positional audio and clarity are praised, especially considering the price.</description></item><item><title>Custom Mechanical Keyboard</title><link>https://DavidDevGear.github.io/reviews/keychron-k10-pro/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://DavidDevGear.github.io/reviews/keychron-k10-pro/</guid><description>Overview The Keychron K10 Pro is a full-size mechanical keyboard known for its hot-swappable switches, QMK/VIA programmability, and multi-device support.
Features Hot-swappable switch support — swap switches without soldering Bluetooth + wired modes QMK/VIA customizable layouts 1000 Hz polling rate and responsive typing feel Drawback Some community feedback suggests occasional quality control issues and customer support limitations, common in affordable custom keyboards.
Verdict Excellent for development and gaming workflows if you value programmability and typing feel, but expect to manage minor quirks.</description></item><item><title>The G14 vs The 5i</title><link>https://DavidDevGear.github.io/reviews/zephyrus-g14-vs-legion-5i/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://DavidDevGear.github.io/reviews/zephyrus-g14-vs-legion-5i/</guid><description>Overview Choosing between the ASUS ROG Zephyrus G14 and the Lenovo Legion 5i (Gen 10) comes down to how you prioritize portability, performance under real workloads, and thermal consistency. Both are widely available on Amazon and consistently praised in professional reviews and user feedback.
Build Quality &amp;amp; Design ASUS ROG Zephyrus G14
Users and reviewers highlight its compact build, solid magnesium alloy chassis, and surprisingly powerful internals for a 14″ gaming laptop.</description></item><item><title>Affiliate Disclosure</title><link>https://DavidDevGear.github.io/disclosure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://DavidDevGear.github.io/disclosure/</guid><description>Transparency &amp;amp; Disclosure Amazon Associates Program Game Dev Gear Reviews is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.com.
What this means:
When you click on Amazon links on this site and make a purchase, I may earn a small commission This comes at no extra cost to you Commissions help support the site and allow me to continue providing detailed reviews Review Integrity Promise I believe in complete transparency.</description></item><item><title>Sweet Spot 1440p Display</title><link>https://DavidDevGear.github.io/reviews/lg-ultragear-27-review/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://DavidDevGear.github.io/reviews/lg-ultragear-27-review/</guid><description>Overview The LG UltraGear 27&amp;quot; ( 27GL850-B / 27GP850-B series) is a well-rounded 1440p gaming monitor with excellent motion performance and vivid color quality.
Performance Users and experts consistently praise its 165 Hz refresh rate and 1ms response times, providing smooth gameplay and low input lag — valuable for both competitive gamers and creators.
Pros Sharp QHD resolution and vibrant Nano IPS panel Great motion clarity and low lag G-SYNC / FreeSync support Cons HDR is basic Contrast and blacks not the deepest Stand may feel stiff to adjust Who It’s For Gamers who want a fast, versatile 27&amp;quot; monitor that can handle shooters, RPGs, and daily productivity — all without huge cost.</description></item><item><title>Classic Gaming Mouse</title><link>https://DavidDevGear.github.io/reviews/logitech-g502-hero/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://DavidDevGear.github.io/reviews/logitech-g502-hero/</guid><description>Overview The Logitech G502 HERO is one of the most popular wired gaming mice of the last decade, known for its precision sensor, programmability, and ergonomic shape.
Design &amp;amp; Ergonomics It’s built for right-handed users, with a thumb rest and comfortable grip, making it suitable for long sessions — whether gaming or designing. The adjustable weights let you customize the feel for your hand and playstyle.
Performance The next-generation HERO sensor delivers up to 25,600 DPI tracking with minimal smoothing or filtering, ensuring precise and responsive input — ideal for competitive gaming.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://DavidDevGear.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://DavidDevGear.github.io/about/</guid><description>About David Game Developer &amp;amp; Hardware Enthusiast I&amp;rsquo;m a solo game developer who has published games on itch.io, Poki, and Crazy Games. I specialize in Godot Engine development with expertise in shaders, optimization, and prototyping.
My Background Game Development Published Games: Multiple titles across various platforms Expertise: Godot Engine, shader programming, game optimization Freelance: Available for Godot development and consulting Hardware Experience Specialization: Game development workstation optimization Focus: What actually matters for development workflow Review Methodology My reviews are based on:</description></item><item><title>Debug JS Loading</title><link>https://DavidDevGear.github.io/debug-js/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://DavidDevGear.github.io/debug-js/</guid><description>Debugging JavaScript Loading Test 1: Check if scripts are in HTML Checking for script tags... Test 2: Direct script test Test JavaScript Function
Test 3: Theme toggle test Toggle Theme (Debug)</description></item><item><title>Feature Test</title><link>https://DavidDevGear.github.io/test/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://DavidDevGear.github.io/test/</guid><description>Testing All Features 1. Theme Toggle (Should Work) This is embedded in header, not via shortcode.
2. Stats Counter 3. Simple Comparison Table Quick Comparison Feature Product A Product B Product C Price $25 $40 $35 Rating 4.5/5 4.3/5 4.4/5 Buttons 6 8 6 Weight 85g 82g 77g 4. Colors Test Neon Blue Electric Purple Card Background 5. JavaScript Test Test JavaScript
6. Current Theme Info Loading theme info...</description></item><item><title>Final Test</title><link>https://DavidDevGear.github.io/final-test/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://DavidDevGear.github.io/final-test/</guid><description>Testing Everything Stats Counter (Should animate when scrolled to) Comparison Table (Should have styling) Colors (Should show with proper theme colors) Neon Blue Electric Purple Card BG Theme Info Current theme: loading&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>JavaScript Test</title><link>https://DavidDevGear.github.io/test-js/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://DavidDevGear.github.io/test-js/</guid><description>Testing JavaScript Loading Theme Toggle Test Test Theme Toggle
Stats Counter Test 0 Test Stat Console Test Test Console</description></item><item><title>Shortcode Test</title><link>https://DavidDevGear.github.io/shortcode-test/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://DavidDevGear.github.io/shortcode-test/</guid><description>Testing if shortcodes work:
Test 1: Simple shortcode Test 2: HTML Red box Test 3: Raw shortcode text</description></item><item><title>Simple Test</title><link>https://DavidDevGear.github.io/test-simple/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://DavidDevGear.github.io/test-simple/</guid><description>Testing with Inline Everything Stats Counter 0 Reviews 0 Products 0 Hours 0 Updates Colors Neon Blue Purple Orange JavaScript Test Test Alert Animate Stats</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://DavidDevGear.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://DavidDevGear.github.io/contact/</guid><description>Feel free to reach out for collaborations, feedback, or questions.
Email: daveadebayo842@gmail.com</description></item><item><title>Image Credits</title><link>https://DavidDevGear.github.io/credits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://DavidDevGear.github.io/credits/</guid><description>I respect the work of photographers and creators whose images are used on this site.
Homepage &amp;amp; Reviews Photos by Ivan Rudoy,Egor Komarov, Roberto Nickson, Artin Bakhan, Amr Taha, Josh Sorenson, Gavin Philips, Kyle Zang, Brandon Romanchuk, Yasin Hasanm, Hamid Roshaan, Jakub Zerdzicki and Joachim Pressl — Unsplash If you are a rights holder and want attribution updated or removed, please contact me.</description></item></channel></rss>